verifiedfile.com 2005-04-04

# MP3 SEARCH ENGINE PRIVACY STATEMENT : DOWNLOAD AUDIO MP3 MUSIC FREE

## Privacy Statement for EarthReactor.com 

**EarthReactor (earthreactor.com)** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for EarthReactor.

#### Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and for security purposes. Your IP may also used to gather demographic information, but is not kept for more than 7 days. All log files are securely overwritten weekly with 7 passes using US DoD 5220.22-M standards. This method ensures files cannot be recovered.  We respect the privacy of our users and will never give out any info

#### Cookies 

Our Site does not use cookies, but an independent company used for advertising may or may not use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad twice.

#### Advertisers 

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information, which contains no personal information unless you willingly provide it. 

#### Registration Forms 

For the protection of our users, we do not require registration.  

#### External Links 

This site contains links to other web sites and file located at other web sites. **EarthReactor** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We are not responsible for material linked in our search service. In simple terms, we provide a search engine solution to finding mp3 files. Please use your judgment when downloading files to prevent infringement upon a copyright.

#### Public Forums 

This site may make available chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We do not contain publicly accessible log file or other information that could be used to identify users. Our log files are overwritten as discussed in the "Information Automatically Logged" section above.

#### Children's Guidelines 

External files or links from **EarthReactor** may contain audio files inappropriate for children. Parental consent is not required to use our services, so children should remain under parental supervision.

#### Information Disclosure

We will never disclose any user information obtained during the operation of our web site to any outside sources whatsoever.

## Contacting EarthReactor 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact the email address provided below: [swishmade@yahoo.com](mailto:swishmade@yahoo.com)

_**This privacy statement was last modified 12/8/2004.**_

 [EarthReactor MP3 Search] [  [EarthReactor Home Page](http://earthreactor.com/) ] [  [ Advertiser's](mailto:swishmade@yahoo.com?subject=Advertise%20on%20Earthreactor) ]  [ About Us ]   
 [Privacy Statement ]   [Advanced MP3 Search ]  [ Submit MP3 Music ]  [ Help ]  [Search Tips ]
